https://www.bgs.com/privacy-policy

Type in your search and press enter
×
AboutOur MissionIndividual LawCar AccidentsCriminal DefenseDivorceDUI & DWI DefenseEnforcement of Out-of-State JudgmentsEstate Planning & Probate & Trust AdministrationFamily LawPersonal InjuryBusiness LawBanking LawCollection LawCommercial LitigationCorporate & Business LawEmployment LawGovernment LawLabor LawMediationReal Estate LawTechnology and Data Privacy LawTransportation LawAttorneysContactCOVID-19
Careers
FAQs
Testimonials
Blog
AboutOur MissionIndividual LawCar AccidentsCriminal DefenseDivorceDUI & DWI DefenseEnforcement of Out-of-State JudgmentsEstate Planning & Probate & Trust AdministrationFamily LawPersonal InjuryBusiness LawBanking LawCollection LawCommercial LitigationCorporate & Business LawEmployment LawGovernment LawLabor LawMediationReal Estate LawTechnology and Data Privacy LawTransportation LawAttorneysTestimonialsContactBlogCareersFAQs
763.780.8500 Toll Free: 800.422.3486 info@bgs.com 200 Coon Rapids Blvd. NW, #400
Coon Rapids, MN 55433
Privacy Policy
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used at www.bgs.com. We take extraordinary steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. By visiting us, you are accepting the privacy policy described below.
Information Collection
We are the sole owner of the information collected from this website. We do not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in the privacy statement below.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor’s hard drive containing information about the visitor. We do not use cookies, but we may link to other websites that use cookies to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. You will want to read the privacy policies of those other websites to see if they use cookies and if they do, how they use them.
Log Files
We keep simple log files to track which pages visitors have viewed and the links they have clicked on. In no way do these log files capture your personal identification or information.
Sharing We do not share any of your personal information with advertisers, merchants, or any other third party.
Links
We are not responsible for the privacy policies of other websites we may link to or that may link to us. Please read the privacy policies of those websites for information on how they use any personal information you provide them. Our privacy policy applies solely to this website. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of other websites.
Website Content
The information shared on this website is intended to provide general information only and should not be used as a substitute for legal counsel or advice. Questions or comments in connection with a particular article may be directed to its author. Other questions or comments regarding this website may be directed to info@bgs.com.
Changes to this Policy
We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our website following the posting of changes to this privacy policy will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the policy that applied at the time the information was collected.
If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us.
Speak with an Experienced Attorney
The law firm of Barna, Guzy & Steffen offers dedicated attorneys who effectively and efficiently handle your legal needs with the highest level of professionalism.
Individual Law
Business Law
Attorneys
Testimonials
Contact
Accessibility StatementPrivacy PolicyWebsite CreditsSitemap
